stop walking like it's weird to walk and
talk at the same time that's weird you
just stand on the street and talk out it
I've had for a second around the street
one side yes one of the great things
about being in Canada as we get a year
of mat leaves and some of the
conversation that comes up is how the
hell does the u.s. not have math leave
but before they look at about that if
you happen to be watching for America
one of the things that is an added bonus
is that you have all these other parents
usually moms who get to take a year off
and so it's a lot easier to meet mom
friends who have babies read rounds rage
I kind of sucked at this and forgot to
do that low so that leaves so I'm not so
great of a story of that but create an
app that allows you to do that so as
best you can re getting the benefits of
the benefits of a year of Matt leave
even if you don't get the year of Matt
leave so that is Apple number 79